He was totally ogling my breasts!
She does have a huge rack,
so they bounce when she runs.
I get why you'd do it, Yoshino-chan.
If there was a button that
would make everyone I hate die,
I probably wouldn't push it.
Gross!
But if there was a button that would
make everyone who hated me die,
Shut up, you guys.
I'd push it without hesitation.
Human Earthworm 3
Creating Humans
Excuse me.
Excuse me!
One adult for Human Earthworm 3.
That'll be 1,800 yen.
Yeah, here.
The show will be starting soon.
I served as a doctor for many years,
working to save lives.
And it turned out he had 50,000 on him!
A middle school brat!
As I was saving countless lives, I found
myself arriving at a particular question.
For real?
This sucks.
That's awesome.
Where does a person's life—
their very soul—actually reside?
So? What'd you do next?
High schoolers shouldn't
skip school to watch movies.
I took it all.
Man, so mean!
Not that I can talk.
That's when I realized it!
This seriously sucks.
The shape of one's soul creates the body!
Then today's your treat!
I can't hear the movie at all.
Screw that.
So I began conducting research on the soul.
We're splitting it even, obviously!
There are always people like that,
even if they vary to some degree.
All alone, in this lab deep in the mountains...
So, were you looking?
I wasn't.
Then are you saying Tsubasa's lying to us?
He was definitely looking at them!
You're nuts, man!
Oh, there's a half-off coupon.
Huh? To where?
Hey! Teach him a lesson first!
Shit.
That woman's just using me to see
where she stands, and she's enjoying it!
You were looking, then.
Damn it.
I'll tell her!
You're not as cute as you
think you are, Tsubasa-san.
These three know that, too.
The only reason they're fawning over you is
because they think you'll let them bang you.
Now to create the perfect human being!
No way.
She won't let us bang her at all.
She's no good anymore.
Stop talking.
S-Stop it!
No!
It's Tsubasa.
Turn off your phone!
Hello?
What's up?
Right now? I'm free.
You three...
Well...
need to mind your manners.
There's no need to worry.
Everything went well.
It's all for the creation of
the perfect human being...
Human Earthworm 3
Creating Humans
Wha...
What is this?
That person just now...
No, a person couldn't do this.
And if they could, would they really
be human?
Monday, 10:10 AM
What if I am the one who did it?
Will you condemn me?
Were those three special to you?
Don't worry.
He can eat it.
Harsh, man!
Poor guy! He's crying now!
Can I...
do that, too?
JUJUTSU KAISEN
Please stay back!
Episode 9:  Small Fry and Reverse Retribution
It seems like the victims
were high school students.
Monday 10:30 AM
Who were those guys?!
Why were they on the scene before forensics?!
One of them was just a kid, too!
I don't know the details, either.
But you saw those stiffs, didn't you?
That's not something a person could do.
Just pretend you never saw it...
If you want to reach retirement
in this line of work, that is.
Can you see it?
This is the residual taint of cursed energy.
No, I can't see anything.
That's because you're not trying to see it.
We typically see curses as
if it's perfectly natural to.
When a cursed technique is used,
it leaves traces behind.
That's what residuals are.
But residuals are much
fainter than cursed spirits.
So focus your vision and look closely.
Oh!
I can see them!
Of course you can.
A proper sorcerer can sense them
before seeing them.
Couldn't you give me a little
more praise or something?
I don't praise or disparage anyone.
I adhere to facts and judge on that basis.
That's who I am.
There was a time when I mistakenly
believed society operated the same way,
but enough about that.
Let's follow them.
Yeah! Let's go all-out!
No, where moderate effort
will suffice, use moderate effort.
Let's go.
We're just not clicking.
I'm not getting anything from him.
I won't be able to lead you this time.
But don't worry. I've called
in a friend you can trust.
This is Nanami Kento,
the ex-salaryman jujutsu sorcerer!
Please don't call me that.
Plenty of jujutsu sorcerers are oddballs,
but since he worked for a company,
he's got a good head on his shoulders.
He's a first-grade sorcerer, too.
I'm sure no one would want to
hear you saying that about them.
A lot of these people wear sunglasses
and stuff to hide their eyes.
Ex-salaryman? Why didn't you become
a jujutsu sorcerer from the start?
We should greet each other first.
Nice to meet you, Itadori-kun.
Oh, yes, nice to meet you, too.
I studied at Jujutsu Tech,
and one thing I learned...
is that jujutsu sorcerers are shit!
Huh?
Then I worked at your typical company,
and one thing I learned
is that work is shit!
Really?!
If both are equally shit,
I'll take the one I'm more suited to.
That's the only reason I came back.
That's dark.
Right?
Itadori-kun, please don't believe
I'm of the same mindset as Gojou-san.
I do trust and have faith in him,
but I do not respect him!
Huh?!
I hate the way the higher-ups do things,
but I believe in rules and regulations.
This conversation is dragging on.
In short, I don't recognize
you as a sorcerer, either.
Even if you do carry the
bomb we know as Sukuna,
please make an effort to
prove that you are useful.
Lately, I've been forced to realize
how weak and useless I am.
But I'll become strong.
I have to be strong, or I won't
be able to choose how I die.
I'll make you recognize me,
even without that advice.
Just give me a bit more time.
Say that to the higher-ups, not me.
Oh, right.
Frankly, I don't care!
Okay, I get it!
There wasn't anything on the
surveillance cameras, right?
Right. There was only one young
man aside from the victims.
Then a cursed spirit was behind it?
Well, most likely.
There's a small chance the
young man could have done it,
but identifying him is the police's—
Lu, lu, lu, lunchbox!
Stop.
I'll take care of this one.
You handle the one over there.
Good detergent!
If you decide you can't beat it, please call me.
Aren't you taking me a bit too lightly here?
It's not a matter of underestimating you or not.
I am an adult, and you are a child.
I have a duty to prioritize
your life over my own.
Lu, lu, lu...
I'd rather you underestimate me
than treat me like a kid.
You've faced several life-or-death situations.
But that does not make you an adult.
Finding more fallen-out hairs on your pillow,
watching your favorite stuffed bread
disappear from the convenience store...
The accumulation of those little despairs
is what makes a person an adult.
JUJUTSU KAISEN
Monday, 11:15 AM
My cursed technique allows me to forcibly
create a weak point on any opponent.
Seven to three.
Striking the point at that ratio
when you draw a line along the
target's length causes a critical hit.
That allows me to deal a fair amount of
damage to those ranked higher than me,
and if their cursed energy is weak,
I can cut them in two, even with a blunt blade.
Are you listening, Itadori-kun?
Huh?! You were talking to me?!
Home run!
Ow...
Is it okay to reveal something like that?
It's no problem to reveal that
technique to that opponent.
Also, all the better if
revealing it misleads them.
I want to focus on the curse,
but it feels like I should be listening.
There is merit to it.
"Revealing one's hand" is a pact that increases
the effectiveness of one's technique.
Like so.
That's all from me.
Wow.
Not only is the blade he used all wrapped up,
but he used the back of it to
slice right through that thing.
Itadori-kun, behind you.
Huh?
I don't like you looking away.
Who's the one distracting me here?!
Detergent!
Your cursed energy comes
up a little slow, huh?
Ow...
Slow?
Your cursed energy can't keep up
with your explosive power.
You're still not good at amassing
cursed energy, so it tends to lag behind.
But that actually creates an
irregular flow of cursed energy.
The moment after your fist strikes,
your cursed energy slams in.
In other words, you're creating
two impacts with every strike.
Divergent Fist
Divergent Fist!
That's so cool!
It's not something many can do on purpose.
This'll be a great weapon for you.
His raw strength is superhuman?
The initial blow has little cursed energy,
but it reaches 120% of
an average sorcerer's power.
Then the real blow of cursed energy flows in.
It must be unimaginably unpleasant
for those struck by it.
He has room to grow, too.
If he can learn to imbue 100% of his
cursed energy into 100% of his martial arts...
Now I see why that man brought him to me.
L-Lu...
Oh, pardon me. I'll end you now.
Itadori-kun! Don't finish it off yet!
Have a look a this.
I took a photo of my opponent.
Huh? I thought cursed spirits
didn't show up in photos.
Please listen calmly.
What we've been fighting...
They're human.
No, I guess I should call them former humans.
They're the same as the three from the theater.
The structure of their bodies was
forcibly altered by a cursed technique.
If that was all, I would
have noticed at the start.
The two we fought were full of
cursed energy, like cursed spirits.
You'll have to ask the culprit about
their cursed technique to explain that.
Though there is evidence that their
brain stems were tampered with,
most likely to create a state of confusion
and impaired consciousness.
If they can tamper with the brain,
it might be possible for them to modify
someone to be able to use cursed energy.
The relationship between the brain
and cursed energy is still a black box to us.
Oh, right, is Itadori listening?
Oh, yeah.
To sum it up, these guys died of shock
from having their bodies modified.
You didn't kill them.
So don't get the wrong idea about that.
Right.
Ieiri Shouko
Either way, the deaths of these two
weigh on me just as heavily.
That said, this thing...
has disgusting taste.
This boy can get sincerely
angry on another's behalf.
Those residuals were a bluff,
likely meant to lure us in.
Our foe is quite skilled.
It looks like this will take
more than moderate effort.
So let's go all-out.
Yeah!
There are cursed spirits known as
special-grade potential apparitions.
Monday, 11:00 AM
Cursed spirits are a collection of the
cursed energy emitted by humans.
Whether it actually exists or not,
a shared image of fear makes it easy
for a powerful curse to manifest.
Complete Guide to
Japanese Apparitions
A shared image of fear?
You mean like famous monsters
and ghost stories?
Yup.
Toilet-bound Hanako-san
Giant Skeleton
Nine-tailed Fox
Like Toilet-bound Hanako-san,
the nine-tailed fox, and so on.
Jujutsu sorcerers have registered them
as special-grade potential apparitions
and keep an eye out for them.
The fact that they often categorize
powerful, unidentified curses
as potential apparitions makes it feel
like that's all they're focused on.
But people constantly fear more
than just those fairy tales, right?
Like natural disasters?
I love how stress-free talking to you is.
No, I'm not...
People...
have always feared the earth,
the forests, and the oceans.
Because the cursed energy directed
toward those is far too big,
they gained wisdom before they took shape
and remained in hiding up until now.
I'm proud to call them all friends.
What kind of curse are you, Mahito-san?
A human one.
I'm a curse that was born from the hatred and
fear people hold in their gut toward others.
Tokyo Municipal
Shuuei High School
Detached Office
I've organized the reports from our windows
Monday 6:25 PM
on recent residuals, unnatural deaths,
and disappearances.
This should help us narrow down
the culprit's hideout to some extent.
Aw yeah! Are we storming in?!
No, it's still only to some extent.
While I continue investigating this matter,
I'd like you to handle a different task.
This is the boy who was at
the theater, Yoshino Junpei.
Apparently, he goes to the same
high school as the victims.
Based on the surveillance footage
and how he carried himself,
I believed it was unlikely
he could be a curse user.
However, if he's related to the
victims, that changes things.
Curse user?
An evil jujutsu sorcerer.
I've entrusted the process to Ijichi-kun, so I'd
like you two to investigate Yoshino Junpei.
Sure!
Speaking of which, I don't know
any assistants other than you.
Well, I'm the only one who knows
you're still alive, so by necessity...
Makes sense.
Let's go!
You already know the location of the culprit,
don't you? And not just "to some extent."
Of course.
If the culprit had wanted, he could have
left the scene without leaving any residuals.
We're being lured in once again.
Weighing the risk of storming in alone
against the risk of taking Itadori-kun with me,
I simply chose the former.
He's still a child, after all.
Nanami-sensei!
Itadori-kun?
I forgot to say something.
Be careful, okay?
Itadori-kun...
I'm not a teacher, so please
don't call me "Sensei."
Nanamin, then!
I will slap you.
There he is.
Huh? Casual clothes?
It looks like he hasn't
attended school for some time.
For Pedestrians
and Bicycles Only
We'll get out of the car here.
Let's go.
Juju Stroll
Nanami! Let's go out together!
No, thank you.
No, s-seriously, I have something
important to talk to you about.
Oh, how awful.
I haven't said anything yet!
Satoru♥
To Nanami
Penis
Episode 10:
Idle Transfiguration